Finding Aid of the UW-Milwaukee Dept. of Enrollment Services Records, 1967-1993
University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee Libraries, Archives Department
UW-Milwaukee Dept. of Enrollment Services Records, 1967-1993
University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee. Dept. of Enrollment Services
UWM Archival Collection 160
1.4 cubic ft. (2 boxes) 55 digital text files (408 MB)
University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee Libraries, Archives Department
Records of the Dept. of Enrollment Services and its sub-units, the Office of the Registrar and the Admissions Office. The collection includes annual reports and planning documents, enrollment statistics, and surveys. The records also document the recruitment of minorities and high school students, and student admission and retention. Also included are electronic copies of the Schedule of Classes from 2008 through Spring 2013.
In 1988, the Dept. of Enrollment Services was established to encompass the Office of the Registrar and the Office of Admissions. Frederick Sperry headed this unit.
The files are organized alphabetically by subject, then chronologically.
The Archives also maintains preservation copies of the Schedule of Classes, which is currently published in electronic form only. See an archivist for details. Copies of the Schedule of Classes are accessible at http://www4.uwm.edu/schedule/.
Administrative/Restriction Information
Electronic files must be viewed on computers in the Archives. Contact an archivist for more information.
There are no access restrictions on the materials, and the collection is open to all members of the public in accordance with state law.
As of December 6, 2016, all electronic files were accessible on a Intel Core i5-4570 CPU (3.20 GHz, 4 GB RAM) running Windows 7 Enterprise, with Service Pack 1. Adobe Acrobat was used to access the files.
The collection includes records in the following file formats:
Portable Document Format [.pdf]
Fred Sperry in Enrollment Services transferred the collection to the Archives in September 1995.
Contents List
- Advisory Committee, Minutes, 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Annual Reports, 1980-1990 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Brochures, 1981-1984, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
- California Reverse Discrimination Case, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- College Board Equality Project, 1985-1988 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Consultants Reports, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Enrollment, 1976-1989 (Box 1, Folder 6-13)
- Enrollment Cap, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Enrollment Ceiling, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Enrollment Projections, 1984-1987 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Fee Cancellations, 1984-1986 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Fees, 1982-1984 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- General Education Requirements, 1983-1987 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Goals, 1986-1989 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- History, 1980, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- In-Person Registration, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- In-Person Registration Task Force, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Marshall Plan, 1983-1986 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Mini-Grants, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Minority Affairs Administrative Committee, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Minority/Disadvantaged Student Life Committee, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Minority Recruitment Review Committee, 1989, undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Minority Student Recruitment, 1983-1988 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Multiple Applicant Study, 1981-1988 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- National Association of College Admissions Counselors, Presentation, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- News Releases, 1971-1985 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Office of the Registrar, Advisory Committee Meeting Minutes, 1985-1987 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Office of the Registrar, Review, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Planning Document, 1982-1991 (Box 1, Folder 34-36)
- Planning for the Future, 1984-1987 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Recruitment, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Refusals, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Registration Report, 1987-1989 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Request for Proposal, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Satellite Instruction Center, 1976, undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Schedule of Classes, 2008-2016
- Standards of Academic Progress, 1977-1983 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Student Recruitment, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Student Retention, 1968-1989 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Student Retention, 1971-1979 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Student Retention Committee, 1975-1979 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Studies, 1971-1984 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Summer Sessions, 1983-1985 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Surveys, 1976-1989 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Surveys, 1983-1989 (Box 2, Folder 12)